<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>

<title>The Groovy Galleon Podcast</title>
<link>https://marksilvermedia.github.io/groovygalleon/podcast</link>
<description>The hip &amp; cool music-oriented podcast by Mark! Silver.</description>

<item>

<title>The Groovy Galleon Podcast - Episode 5: The Jamendo Variety Show</title>

<link>https://archive.org/download/ggpod5/gge5.flac</link>
<guid>https://archive.org/download/ggpod5/gge5.flac</guid>

<pubDate>2017-08-12</pubDate>

<description>The biggest of the tech giants in silicon valley are hellbent on censoring people who don't fit the narratives they want to push. Luckily, I avoid these particular giants like the plague, so the Groovy Galleon Podcast will continue to thrive.</description>

<enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/ggpod5/gge5.flac" type="audio/flac"/>

</item>
  
<item>

<title>The Groovy Galleon Podcast - Episode 4: A Comprehensive History of Ska Music</title>

<link>https://archive.org/download/marksilvermedia_protonmail_Gge4/gge4.flac</link>
<guid>https://archive.org/download/marksilvermedia_protonmail_Gge4/gge4.flac</guid>

<pubDate>2017-08-05</pubDate>

<description>Y'know, this may make me sound behind my times, but I miss the old days. What ever happened to the days of music with an oversaturation of brass, woodwind, and the "skank" guitar rhythm in an otherwise standard rock world? That kind of stuff should totally make a comeback. Today, on the Groovy Galleon Podcast, I will be taking a retrospective look back into the ska genre, by reviewing albums that were released at different points in its evolution; from the classic ska sound, to the 2 Tone genre, to modern day Ska-punk.</description>

<enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/marksilvermedia_protonmail_Gge4/gge4.flac" type="audio/flac"/>

</item>
  
<item>

<title>The Groovy Galleon Podcast - Episode 3: Went Shopping at the Minimall</title>

<link>https://archive.org/download/GroovyGalleonE3/gge3.flac</link>
<guid>https://archive.org/download/GroovyGalleonE3/gge3.flac</guid>

<pubDate>2017-07-29</pubDate>

<description>I do possess a finely-tuned intellegence which tells me that you're listening to the Groovy Galleon Podcast. For today's episode, I did an interview with the kitsch-pop band "Minimall". It was a bunch of fun, so you should totally check it out!</description>

<enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/GroovyGalleonE3/gge3.flac" type="audio/flac"/>

</item>

<item>

<title>The Groovy Galleon Podcast - Episode 2: Celebrate American Independence with Japanese Jazz Fusion</title>

<link>https://archive.org/download/marksilvermedia_protonmail_Gge2/gge2.flac</link>
<guid>https://archive.org/download/marksilvermedia_protonmail_Gge2/gge2.flac</guid>

<pubDate>2017-07-15</pubDate>

<description>We hold these truths to be self-evident, that all men are created equal, that they are endowed by their Creator with certain unalienable Rights, that among these are Life, Liberty, the pursuit of Happiness, and of course, the right to listen to the hip and cool music-oriented podcast known by no other name than the Groovy Galleon. My name is Mark! Silver (the exclamation point is of course silent), and you are listening to episode two of this podcast.</description>

<enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/marksilvermedia_protonmail_Gge2/gge2.flac" type="audio/flac"/>

</item>

<item>

<title>The Groovy Galleon Podcast - Episode 1: Sometimes, the cat shivers.</title>

<link>https://archive.org/download/groovygalleonE1/gge1.flac</link>
<guid>https://archive.org/download/groovygalleonE1/gge1.flac</guid>

<pubDate>2017-06-25</pubDate>

<description>Holy new podcast, Batman! Today, Mark! (the exclamation point is silent) begins his podcasting journey by reviewing music; most of which you probably haven't heard of. This episode begins with an obligatory short introduction before taking a look into the latest Foresters album. Mark then gives a lengthy in-depth review/analysis/something of the brand spankin' new Sometimes the Cat album. Lastly, we get to hear the start of Mark's compact disc collection before he goes into detail about the process of creating his Roadtrip 2017 album (as well as an HTML/CSS-based bandcamp alternative).</description>

<enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/groovygalleonE1/gge1.flac" type="audio/flac"/>

</item>

</channel>
</rss>
